We created an extension about original date.
I think I want to have some improvements,
so have publication data for this article, right?
But sometimes it's like very visible.
I see November 70, 2025, but still not working.
So just use car, sir.
And I'll copy the others URL, this one.
And my extension doesn't detect a data.
Even though it's clearly seen, there is a data at the top.
Maybe we can add a shown layer that will detect shortcuts
or elements trying to gasellate,
because address we see here is.
And I'll switch to agents basically.
I will copy it, open a new agent.
Go back to the agent that we'll see.
In November 2075, OK?
November 17, 2025.
And open a new agent, so it will just create.
I want you to add a feature that will allow us
to change a date format for, you know, to maybe it's
for American, so you have the name of the day
and include other years.
Like tie here, Arabic, et cetera.
Maybe other people from the community would like to use
and use other days.
For example, now I'm in Thailand, so I know it's 2,567.
So at this, and we see this to-do list,
we have improved data detection, you see how it works.
OK, so it's using public available information.
We have put this, we have a Japanese day, Chinese,
numeric long, we have an hour format and other stuff.
It's still playing the next moves, so let's wait.
I've seen you format the Buddhist calendar conversion,
Japanese era, Hindi, Chinese.
So now I will just try to sit in the updates, so I will refresh it,
reload it, original data.
And now, OK, it seems now with the text publication
in the middle format, this page may contain date metadata.
So I will just refresh it.
OK, we see it.
What's added about the text, I have no idea how we can set it.
So I'll just post screenshot.
OK, but the problem is, how can I switch?
Because I see on the current date panel.
OK, let's see now updates now.
I will go again, and I will update an extension.
After we see, I can switch directly here,
table this Japanese, we have a Islamic calendar, Chinese default
and it switches dynamically.
So this way, we can actually create very nice extension.
And obviously, it will work across all the signs.
I don't know the date, but I can press it.
And I see publication date.
And under future, we can add is, if you know exact time,
you can add it on the right of date, if not,
you don't write anything.
So it would be just simple.
It would just add a small feature for it.
Now we'll refresh the extension.
And if I press it, OK, I even see the time.
So you detect it.
That's great.
And it displays even the time zones for other date formats.
So this is default, send for PMAM.
And yeah, this way we can adjust it.
Because for example, here it's just 7am, this is another format.
Actually, it detects because this one is European,
so you are not using 7pm.
But if you press mouth, we press another one.
Or here, it will try to check it.
It detects some other formats, right?